drsircus.com 2019-04-06

# Privacy Policy | Dr. Sircus

## Privacy Policy for drsircus.com

### Effective Date: 06/07/2018

### Last Modified Date: 10/25/2018

This policy describes the ways in which we collect, store, use and protect your personal information. You agree to such policy and agree to such collection, storage and use when subscribing to or using our products, services or any other feature, technology or functionality that we offer when accessing our site or otherwise (collectively "the Services of Brain Power ").

We may change this policy at any time by posting a revised version on our site. The revised version will take effect as it becomes available on the site. In addition, if the revised version includes a substantial change, we will notify you 30 days in advance by posting notice of the change on the Policy Updates page of our site. After this 30 day notice, you will be deemed to agree to all amendments made to this policy.

This Privacy Notice contains the following information, which you can access by scrolling down:

  1. Important: Opt-Out Policy
  2. How We Collect Information
  3. How We Use Cookies
  4. Google Remarketing
  5. How We Protect and Store Personal Information
  6. How We Use the Personal Information We Collect
  7. Marketing
  8. How We Share Personal Information With Others
  9. How to contact us

## Important: Opt-Out Policy

The user of our services may at any time stop receiving communications from our site. To do so simply send an email to sup´port@drsircus.com indicating your desire to no longer receive communications, or simply click on the ‘remove’ or ‘unsubscribe’ link contained at the end of each email.

## How We Collect Information

When you visit drsircus.com website or use the Services of drsircus.com, we collect your IP address and standard web access information such as the type of your browser and the pages you have accessed on our site.

If you sign up we will collect the following types of information:

Contact information – your name and email.

Financial Information – We do not keep any financial information from client when buying at our site [www.drsircus.com](https://www.drsircus.com/).

When you use the Services of drsircus.com, we will collect information about your transactions and other activities on our website or when using the Services of drsircus.com we may collect information about your computer or other access device for the purpose of preventing fraud.

Finally, we may collect additional information from and about you by other means, such as contacting our customer support team, the results of your responses to a survey, interactions with members of drsircus.com team, and other companies.

## How We Use Cookies

When you access our site, we, including the companies we hire to track how our site is used, may place small data files called "cookies" on your computer.

We send a "session cookie" to your computer when you log into your account or use your BUSINESS SERVICES This type of cookie helps us recognize you if you visit multiple pages on our site during the same session, so that we do not need request your password on all pages. After you quit or close your browser, this cookie will expire and will no longer take effect.

We also use more permanent cookies for other purposes such as displaying your email address on our login form, so you do not have to re-enter the email address every time you sign in to your account. We encrypt our cookies so that only we can interpret the information stored in them. You are free to decline our cookies if your browser allows, but this may interfere with the use of our site.

We and our service providers also use cookies to personalize our services, content and advertising, evaluate the effectiveness of promotions, and promote trust and security.

You may find third-party cookies when using the Copywrite Services on certain sites that are not under our control (for example, if you view a web page created by a third party or use an application developed by a third party, a cookie may be placed by that page or application).

## Google Remarketing

We use the Google Adwords Remarketing feature to serve ads on Google partner sites. This feature allows you to identify that you have visited our site and so Google can display our ad for you on different websites. A number of third-party vendors, including Google, buy advertising space on Internet sites. We eventually hire Google to display our ads in those spaces. To identify your visit on our site, other suppliers

of third parties, as well as Google, use cookies, in a similar way to the one exposed in the section "How we use cookies". You can disable Google’s use of cookies by accessing the Ads Preferences Manager.

## How We Protect and Store Personal Information

Throughout this policy, we use the term "personal information" to describe information that may be associated with a particular person and can be used to identify that person. We will not treat personal information as information that should remain anonymous so that it does not identify a particular user.

We store and process your personal information on our computers and protect them under physical, electronic and procedural safeguards. We use computer protections such as firewalls and authorize access to personal information only to employees who need them to fulfill their professional responsibilities.

## How We Use the Personal Information We Collect

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, secure, efficient, and personalized experience. To do this, we use your personal information to:

• provide the requested services and customer support;

• process transactions and send notices about your transactions

• settle disputes, charge fees and troubleshoot;

• prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities and ensure the application of our User Agreement;

• customize, evaluate and improve our services, in addition to the content and layout of our site;

• send targeted marketing materials, service update notices and promotional offers based on your communication preferences;

## Marketing

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes in any reason. We may combine your information with the information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize our services, content and advertising. If you do not wish to receive our marketing messages or participate in our ad customization programs, simply indicate your preference by sending us an email or simply clicking the unsubscribe link provided in all our emails.

## How We Share Personal Information With Others

We may share your personal information with: drsircus.com team members to provide joint content, products and services (such as registration, transactions, and customer support) to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and violations of our policies, in addition to cooperating in the decisions regarding its products, services and communications. Members of our corporate family will use this information to send you marketing communications only if you have requested their services. Suppliers of contract services that collaborate in parts of our business operations; (fraud prevention, collection activities, marketing, technology services). Our contracts require that these service providers only use your information in relation to the services they perform for us, not for their own benefit.

Companies with which we intend to merge or acquire. (If a merger occurs, we will require the new entity to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information.)

Police officers, government officials or other third parties when:

• we are required to do so by subpoena, court order or similar legal process,

• we must do so in order to comply with law or credit card association rules

• we are cooperating

• We believe in good faith that the disclosure of personal information is necessary to prevent physical damage or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity, or to investigate violations of our User Agreement.

• Other third parties with your consent or guidance.

Note that these third parties may be in other countries where the law on the processing of personal information is less rigid than that of your country.

In cases where our company and a partner promote our Services together, we may disclose to the partner some personal information such as the name, address and username of the persons who have registered with our Services as a result of the joint promotion for the sole purpose of enabling us and the partner to evaluate the results of the promotion. In that case, personal information may not be used by the partner for any other purpose

Drsircus.com will not sell or lease any of your personal information to third parties in the ordinary course of business and will only share your personal information with third parties as described in this policy.

If you subscribe to drsircus.com directly on a third party site or through a third party application, any information entered on that site or application (and not directly on a drsircus.com website) will be shared with the owner of that site or application – and your information may be subject to their privacy policies.

## How to contact us

If you have any questions or concerns about our use of your personal information, please do not hesitate to contact us through any of the methods listed below. If you have a complaint or concern about how we are using your personal information, then we will work to address such concern(s).

Mail:

Address 1: Sítio Santuário s/n

Address 2: Povoado do Moinho

City/State: Alto Paraíso, Goiás

Postal Number: 73770000 – Brazil

Email: support@drsircus.com
